Guide to the Office of Residential Life records, 1946-2012 and undated UA.09.06.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Office of Residential Life records
1946-2012 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. Residence Life and Housing Services
UA.09.06.0002
29 Linear Feet
The Office of Residential Life has long been committed to creating an active and meaningful residential life for its students. As such, it has continuously worked to review and improve the quality of residential life at Duke University. Materials in the collection include administrative records, correspondence, meeting minutes, financial and statistical reports, memoranda, proposals, newsletters, handbooks, color slides, computer diskettes, reel-to-reel audio recordings, survey results and other materials documenting the activities of the Office of Residential Life.
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
For a period of twenty-five years from the origin of the material, permission in writing from the office of origin and the University Archivist is required for use of administrative records. After twenty-five years, records that have been processed may be consulted with the permission of the University Archivist.
In accordance with the Family Education Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) of 1974 as amended, Duke University permits students to inspect their educational records and limits the disclosure of personally identifiable information from education records.
Electronic records in this collection have been migrated to a library server and digital use copies can only be accessed onsite in the Rubenstein Library Reading Room. To request access, please contact Research Services before coming to use these records.
Provenance
The Office of Residential Life records, 1946-2000 and undated were received by the University Archives in a series of transfers from 1978 to 20017.
Historical Note
The Office of Residential Life (currently named Residence Life and Housing Services) has long been committed to creating an active and meaningful residential life for its students. As such, it has continuously worked to review and improve the quality of residential life at Duke University. Historically, the it has addressed the effects of overcrowding, the selection process for residence halls, the separation of men on West Campus in both all-freshman and cross-sectional housing and women on East Campus in cross-sectional housing, freshman orientation, and administrative policies and guidelines.
A few of its more prominent programs include Duke University Experiential Living/Learning (D.U.E.L.L.), an alternative living opportunity based on the philosophy of Outward Bound; Duke's Vision Program, a program created in 1989 to introduce the diversity of the Duke Community and the University's commitment to multicultural diversity to entering freshman; and the formation of SHARE, an experimental living-learning project and Duke's first co-educational dorm on East Campus. In addition to these programs, there have been numerous committees appointed to review residential life and to make recommendations to improve the quality of residential living for students.
Collection Overview
The Office of Residential Life records spans the years 1946-2012 and undated. Materials in the collection include administrative records, correspondence, meeting minutes, financial and statistical reports, memoranda, proposals, newsletters, handbooks, color slides, computer diskettes, reel-to-reel audio recordings, survey results and other materials documenting the activities of the Office of Residential Life. The collection is arranged alphabetically, with the exception of four boxes (Box 32, Box 33, Box 34 and Box 35). Three diskettes (Disk001, Disk002 and Disk003) were removed from Box 17 and migrated to the electronic records server. In addition, Box 35 is stored off-site.
Related Material
Alspaugh Residence Hall Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Baldwin Federation Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Bassett Residence Hall Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Gilbert-Addoms Residence Hall Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Interfraternity Council Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Jarvis House Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Living Groups Reference Collection, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
SHARE Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Residential Program Review Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Residence and education; Dormitories -- North Carolina; Student housing -- North Carolina -- Durham; College freshmen -- North Carolina -– Durham; College students -- North Carolina -- Durham; College student orientation -- North Carolina -- Durham; Duke University. Office of Residential Life; Duke University. Residence Life and Housing Services; Duke University. Woman's College
- Academic Dishonesty Policy, 1962-1963 (Box 1)
- Adams, James L. (Director, General Services), Correspondence, 1968-1972 (Box 1)
- ADSU (Associated Students of Duke University), 1966-1971 and undated (Box 1)
- AIH Independent Self-Study Committee Report, 1969 Apr (Box 1)
- Alcoholic Beverage Regulations, 1960-1972 (Box 1)
- Alumnae Weekend, 1968-1972 (Box 1)
- Annual Treasurer's Report (budget), Bassett House, 1949-1972 (Box 1)
- Annual Treasurer's Report (budget), Jarvis House, 1963-1971 (Box 1)
- Annual Treasurer's Report (budget), Phi Kappa Delta, 1957-1969 (Box 1)
- Application for Student Coordinator - D.U.E.L.L., 1986 (Box 1)
- Articles on Residential Life, 1983-1984 (Box 1)
- Articles on Residential Life, 1984-1985 (Box 1)
- Articles on Residential Life, 1985-1986 (Box 1)
- Articles on Residential Life, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
- Articles on Residential Life, 1987-1988 (Box 2)
- Articles on Residential Life, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
- Articles on Residential Life, 1989-1990 (Folder 1) (Box 2)
- Articles on Residential Life, 1989-1990 (Folder 2) (Box 2)
- Assistant Dean of Women Information (Handbook), 1959 (Box 2)
- AWS Ad Hoc Committee on Housing, undated (Box 2)
- Background Information - Duke's Vision Program, 1989-1990 (Box 2)
- Black/White Relations Task Force, 1982 (Box 2)
- Bulletin of Duke Residential Staff, 1974-1975 (Box 2)
- Bulletin of Duke University Residential Staff, 1975-1976 (Box 2)
- Bulletin of Duke University Residential Staff, 1976-1977 (Box 3)
- Bulletin of Men's Residential Staff, 1972-1973 (Box 3)
- Bulletin of Men's Residential Staff, 1973-1974 (Box 3)
- Building Security Task Force, 1989 (Box 3)
- Campus Community Council (CCC) Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 3)
- Campus Community Council (CCC) Minutes, 1971-1972 (Box 3)
- Campus Community Council (CCC) Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 3)
- Campus Community Council (CCC) Proposals, 1971-1972 (Box 3)
- Black/White Relations Task Force, 1982 (Box 3)
- CAPS (Counseling & Psychological Services) Advisory Committee, 1977-1979 (Box 3)
- Celebrate Duke University Event, 1993 (Box 4)
- Celestial Omnibus, 1968 (Box 4)
- Central Campus Housing Facility, 1985-1987 (Box 4)
- Chronicle Articles on Residential Life, 1982-1983 (Box 4)
- Chronicle - Residential Life Articles, 1981-1982 (Box 4)
- Cleaveland, Frederic (Provost) Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 4)
- Cleland - SAE Disputes, 1982 (RESTRICTED) (Box 4)
- Commencement, 1969-1972 (Box 4)
- Committee on Use of University Facilities, 1971 (Box 4)
- Community Council of the Women's College (CCWC) Questionnaire, 1971 (Box 4)
- Commons Rooms, 1968-1972 (Box 4)
- Conscientious Objectors & Draft Counseling, undated (Box 4)
- Constitution - Congress of Racial Equality (CORE), 1963 (Box 4)
- Constitutions of Campus Organizations, 1950-1970 and undated (Box 4)
- Constitutions - MSGA, IFC, 1967-1970 and undated (Box 4)
- Correspondence (Men's College), 1968-1973 (Box 4)
- Correspondence (Women's College), 1958-1981 (Box 5)
- Corridors, 1966-1969 and undated (Box 5)
- Corridors - Afro-American Studies Hall (proposed), 1969-1970 (Box 5)
- Corridors - Contemporary Arts, 1967-1970 (Box 5)
- Corridors - Experimental (Women's), 1961-1968 (Box 5)
- Corridors - French, 1964-1972 (Box 5)
- Corridors - Humanities, 1965 (Box 5)
- Corridors - Science, 1966 (Box 5)
- Council of Freshmen Presidents, 1982-1987 (Box 5)
- Counselors' Materials - Orientation, 1971 (Box 5)
- Damages Policies, 1969-1973 (Box 5)
- Dean of Woman's College Correspondence with House Counselors, 1954-1972 (Folder 1) (Box 5)
- Dean of Woman's College Correspondence with House Counselors, 1954-1972 (Folder 2) (Box 6)
- Dean of Woman's College Correspondence with House Counselors, 1954-1972 (Folder 3) (Box 6)
- Dean of Woman's College Correspondence with House Counselors, 1954-1972 (Folder 4) (Box 6)
- Dean of Woman's College - Publishing: 1968-1969, A Report on the New IBM Selectronic Typsetting Equipment, undated (Box 6)
- Dean of Woman's College - Residential Manual, 1970-1971 (Box 6)
- Dining Services, 1968-1972 (Box 6)
- Dorm Housing, 1982-1986 (Box 6)
- Dormitory - Constitutions, 1966-1970 (Box 6)
- Dormitory Fire Procedures & Drills, 1968-1975 (Box 7)
- Dormitory Policies, 1963-1972 (Box 7)
- Dormitory Renovations, 1963-1972 (Box 7)
- Drug Policy, 1968-1970 (Box 7)
- D.U.E.L.L. (Duke University Experiential Living/Learning) Houses, 1983-1986 (Box 7)
- D.U.E.L.L. End of Year Report Materials, 1986-1989 and undated (Box 7)
- Durham Hotel, 1972 (Box 7)
- East Campus Regulations, 1953 (Box 7)
- Exam Book (Duke's Vision), 1990 (Box 7)
- Expense Accounts (D.U.E.L.L.), 1983-1986 (Box 7)
- Experiential Education Info, undated (Box 7)
- Faculty Discussion Leaders (Duke's Vision), 1990 (Box 7)
- Faculty Discussion Leaders (Duke's Vision), 1991 (Box 7)
- Faculty Discussion Leaders (Duke's Vision), 1992 (Box 7)
- Faculty Fellows of Trinity College Proposal, 1964 (Box 8)
- Federations Floor Plans, undated (Box 8)
- Federations Planning, 1970-1974 (Box 8)
- Federations Proposals, 1969-1971 (Box 8)
- Final Report on Freshman Clusters, 1982 (Box 8)
- Financial - Miscellaneous Cash Fund, 1971-1972 (Box 8)
- Financial Statements - D.U.E.L.L., 1983-1984 (Box 8)
- Financial Statements - D.U.E.L.L., 1984-1985 (Box 8)
- Financial Statements - D.U.E.L.L., 1983-1986 (Box 8)
- Flyers, Ads, Program Information (D.U.E.L.L.), 1983-1986 and undated (Box 8)
- Formal Rush, 1969-1972 (Box 8)
- Fraternities (Rush Advisors: Freshmen), 1969-1971 (Box 8)
- Fraternity/Freshmen Cross-Sectional Questionnaire, 1970-1971 (Box 8)
- Fraternity/Freshmen Experiment Procedures, 1969-1970 (Box 8)
- Fraternity Pledges, 1974 (Box 8)
- Freshman Cabinet Minutes, 1968-1969 (Box 9)
- Freshman Counseling Data Sheet, 1969-1970 (Box 9)
- Freshman Government Officers & Cabinet, 1967-1970 (Box 9)
- Freshman Housing, 1971-1973 (Box 9)
- Freshman Orientation, 1974 (Box 9)
- GPA's 1976-1991 (Box 9)
- Greek Organizations - Consumer Research Surveys, 1971-1974 (Box 9)
- Greek Organizations - Inter-fraternity Council (IFC), 1970-1972 (Box 9)
- Greek Organizations - Inter-fraternity Council (IFC) Procedures, 1969-1971 (Box 9)
- Greek Organizations - Legal Issues, 1956-1970 (Box 9)
- Greek Organizations - Panhellenic Council Correspondence, 1966-1975 (Box 9)
- Greek Organizations - Panhellenic Council Minutes, 1960-1966 (Box 9)
- Greek Organizations - Rush Information, 1965-1971 (Box 9)
- Greek Organizations - Sororities, 1946-1972 (Box 10)
- Greek Organizations - Sororities Correspondence, 1957-1967 (Box 10)
- Greek Organizations - Sororities Membership Lists, 1970-1974 (Box 10)
- Greek Organizations - Sororities Rush Information, 1966-1969 (Box 10)
- Holidays/Breaks (Staffing), 1973-1974 (Box 10)
- House Course Handouts, 1984 (Box 10)
- House Course Information, 1983-1985 (Box 10)
- House Dues, 1971-1972 (Box 10)
- House Officers, 1976-1981 (Box 11)
- House Officers, 1984-1985 (Box 11)
- House Officers, 1985-1986 (Box 11)
- House Presidents, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
- House Presidents Board Adviser Notebook, 1954-1970 (Box 11)
- Housemaster Handbook, 1970 (Box 11)
- Housemaster Program, 1963 and undated (Box 11)
- Housing Correspondence, 1968-1978 (Box 11)
- Housing Declarations, 1973-1975 (Box 11)
- Housing Forms & Correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box 11)
- Housing Lease Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
- Housing Management, 1969-1973 (Box 11)
- House Management, 1975-1982 (Box 12)
- Housing Policies and Procedures, 1973-1985 (Box 12)
- Housing Policies and Procedures, 1985-1987 (Box 12)
- Housing Policies and Procedures, 1987-1989 (Box 12)
- Housing Statistics, 1975-1984 (Box 12)
- Housing Statistics, 1984-1985 (Box 13)
- Housing Statistics, 1985-1986 (Box 13)
- Housing Statistics, 1986-1987 (Box 13)
- Housing Statistics, 1987-1988 (Box 13)
- Housing Statistics, 1988-1989 (Box 14)
- Housing Statistics, 1989-1990 (Box 14)
- IFC (Interfraternity Council), 1966-1970 (Box 14)
- Interfraternity Council, 1969 (Box 14)
- International Students, 1964-1974 (Box 14)
- Jarvis House, 1972-1983 and undated (Box 14)
- Joint Statement on Rights and Freedoms of Students, 1967-1968 (Box 14)
- Judicial Code Committee, 1969-1970 and undated (Box 14)
- Judicial Review Committee, 1971 (Box 14)
- Kilgo Federation Executive Council Minutes, 1971-1973 (Box 14)
- License to Occupy Residence Hall Space, 1972-1973 (Box 15)
- Living/Learning (5th/6th Semester), 1983-1984 (Box 15)
- Living/Learning (7th/8th Semester), 1984-1985 (Box 15)
- Living/Learning (9th/10th Semester), 1985 (Box 15)
- Living/Learning (11th Semester), 1986 (Box 15)
- Living/Learning Articles, 1981-1985 (Box 15)
- Living/Learning (11th Semester) Budget, 1986 (Box 15)
- Living/Learning Development Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 15)
- Living/Learning Info Sheets, 1983-1988 (Box 15)
- Living/Learning Slides, 1983-1986 and undated (Box 15)
- Lottery for Housing Assignments (Men), 1974-1975 (Box 15)
- Lottery for Housing Assignments (Women), 1974-1975 (Box 15)
- M-Earp (Medication-Evaluation & Research Program), 1975-1976 (Box 15)
- Making it Happen: A Guide to Residential Programming, 1983 (Box 15)
- Manual for the Treasurers of Student Organizations, 1970-1971 (Box 15)
- Mary Duke Biddle Room, 1960-1963, 19736 (Box 15)
- Materials for Evans Enrollment Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 15)
- Multicultural Task Force, 1989 (Box 15)
- New Curriculum, 1969 (Box 16)
- Newspaper Articles (Duke's Vision), 1989 (Box 16)
- Newspaper Articles (Duke's Vision), 1990-1991 (Box 16)
- Notes for House Counselors (Handbook), 1968 Sep (Box 16)
- Notes for House Counselors (Handbook), 1969 Jan (Box 16)
- Notes for House Counselors (Handbook), 1971 Sep (Box 16)
- Notes to Counselors, 1973-1974 (Box 16)
- Notes to House Counselors (Handbook), 1967 (Box 16)
- Notes to House Counselors (Handbook), 1968 Jan (Box 16)
- Off Campus Facilities for Sororities, 1971 (Box 16)
- Omega House, 1971 and undated (Box 16)
- Open Houses (visitation), 1965-1971 (Box 16)
- Orientation, 1989 (Box 16)
- Orientation, 1990 (Box 16)
- Orientation, 1991 (Box 17)
- Orientation, 1992 (Box 17)
- Orientation, 1993 (Box 17)
- Orientation Event Flyer, 1993; 1 PageMaker document; approximately 1 megabytes.
  Scope and Contents
  A flyer for an art performance event at Duke Chapel Steps on August 29, 1993.
- Panel Discussions, 1972 (Box 17)
- Pet Regulations, 1971 (Box 17)
- Planning - New Dormitories, 1954-1968 (Box 17)
- Presentations (Duke's Vision), 1990 (Box 17)
- President's Letters (Terry Sanford), 1970-1972 (Box 17)
- Privacy Policy of Student Rooms, 1970-1971 (Box 17)
- Program II, 1969-1970 (Box 17)
- Program Management Department, 1970-1971 (Box 17)
- Proposed Development of Housing Management Guidelines, 1972 (Box 17)
- Public Safety Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 17)
- Publications (Duke's Vision), 1989 (Box 18)
- Publications (Duke's Vision), 1992 (Box 18)
- Purchasing, 1968-1972 (Box 18)
- Quad Parties, 1973 (Box 18)
- Refrigerator Policy, 1970-1972 (Box 18)
- Regulations on Pickets, Protests & Demonstrations, 1968-1969 (Box 18)
- Relocation Information, 1982-1984 (Box 18)
- Reorganization Committee (D.U.E.L.L.), 1986 (Box 18)
- Report of Mary Grace Wilson (Dean, Undergraduate Women), 1969-1970 (Box 18)
- Report to President, 1948-1949, 1952-1953 (Box 18)
- Report to President, 1960-1968 (Box 18)
- Residence Hall Agreements, 1971-1973 (Box 18)
- Residence Hall Programming (Freshmen & Upperclass), 1982-1985 (Box 19)
- Residence Hall Programming - General, 1985-1987 (Box 19)
- Residence Hall Questionnaire, 1971 (Box 19)
- Residence Hall Regulations - Social Regulations, 1973-1974 (Box 19)
- Residence Hall Regulations - Visitation Policy, 1970-1972 (Box 19)
- Residential Adviser Applicants, 1975-1977 (Box 19)
- Residential Life - Miscellaneous Materials, 1961-1969 (Box 19)
- Residential Governance Study Committee - Commission Survey, 1971-1976 (Box 19)
- Residential Governance Study Committee - Minutes, 1969-1972 (Box 19)
- Residential Governance Study Committee - Proposals & Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 20)
- Residential Governance Study Committee - Working Files, 1971-1972 (Box 20)
- Residential Life Committee, 1968-1970 (Box 20)
- Residential Life Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 20)
- Residential Life Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 20)
- Residential Life Committee, 1969-1974 (Box 20)
- Residential Life Committee, 1974 (Box 20)
- Residential Life Committee - Article Abstracts, undated (Box 20)
- Residential Life Committee - Articles, 1971 and undated (Box 20)
- Residential Life Committee - Bibliography, 1968 (Folder 1) (Box 21)
- Residential Life Committee - Bibliography, 1968 (Folder 2) (Box 21)
- Residential Life Committee - Conference (Residential College Concept in American Higher Education), 1967 (Box 21)
- Residential Life Committee - Correspondence/Memoranda, 1968-1973 (Box 21)
- Residential Life Committee - Drafts, 1969 (Box 21)
- Residential Life Committee - Evaluation, 1971-1972 (Box 21)
- Residential Life Committee - Living/Learning Corridors, 1970-1971 (Box 21)
- Residential Life Committee - Minutes, 1968-1973 (Box 21)
- Residential Life Committee - Proposal for Coed Dorms for the Fall, 1971 (Box 21)
- Residential Life Committee - Proposals & Reports, 1964-1973 (Folder 1) (Box 21)
- Residential Life Committee - Proposals & Reports, 1964-1973 (Folder 2) (Box 22)
- Residential Life Committee - Proposals & Reports, 1964-1973 (Folder 3) (Box 22)
- Residential Life Committee - Questionnaire, 1971 (Box 22)
- Residential Life Committee - Report of the Committee for Study of Student Residential Life, 1969 Jul (Box 22)
- Residential Life Committee - Residential Programs at Other Institutions, 1968 (Box 22)
- Residential Life Committee - Statistics, 1968-1971 (Box 22)
- Residential Life Committee - Student Interviews, 1968-1971 (Box 22)
- Residential Life Committee - Sub-Committees, 1968-1970 (Box 22)
- Residential Life Housing Assignment Policies, 1983-1989 (Box 22)
- Residential Life Housing Assignment Policies, 1990-1993 (Box 22)
- Residential Life Housing Statistics, 1975-1981 (Box 22)
- Residential Life Survey, 1973-1974 (Box 22)
- Residential Life Task Force - Final Report, 1980 (Box 23)
- Residential Policy Committee, 1992 (Box 23)
- Residential Policy Committee - Draft Report, 1992 (Box 23)
- Residential Policy Committee - Proposals & Evaluations, 1992 (Box 23)
- Residential Program Review, 1999 (Box 23)
- Residential Staff - Alspaugh House, 1962-1972 (Box 23)
- Residential Staff - Aycock House, 1963-1973 (Box 23)
- Residential Staff - Baldwin Federation, 1972-1973 (Box 23)
- Residential Staff - Bassett House, 1967-1971 (Box 23)
- Residential Staff - Brown House, 1962-1971 (Box 23)
- Residential Staff - Broughton House (K&L), 1971-1973 (Box 23)
- Residential Staff - Cleland, 1971-1974 (Box 23)
- Residential Staff - Epworth, 1963-1973 (Box 23)
- Residential Staff - Financial Information, 1969-1971 (Box 23)
- Residential Staff - Gilbert-Addoms, 1957-1980 (Box 23)
- Residential Staff - House Counselors Information, 1971-1973 (Box 23)
- Residential Staff - Incident Reports, 1972-1975 (Box 23)
- Residential Staff - Interview Schedules, 1971-1976 (Box 23)
- Residential Staff - Notebook for House Counselors, 1973-1974 (Box 23)
- Residential Staff - Orientation Materials and Evaluation, 1974-1975 (Box 23)
- Residential Staff - Orientation Program, 1975-1976 (Box 23)
- Residential Staff - Personnel/Affirmative Action Program, 1971 (Box 23)
- Residential Staff - Residential Advisor Leadership Skills Workshop, 1975 Aug (Box 24)
- Residential Staff - Residential Advisor Manual, 1975 (Box 24)
- Residential Staff - Residential Advisor Programs, 1975 (Box 24)
- Residential Staff - Self-Evaluations, 1975 (Box 24)
- Residential Staff - Small Group Meetings, 1974 (Box 24)
- Residential Staff - Student Employment, 1957-1970 (Box 24)
- Residential Staff - Wilson House, 1972-1975 (Box 24)
- Residential Survey - Alspaugh-Broughton, 1971-1973 (Box 24)
- Residential Survey - Brown-Cleland, 1971-1973 (Box 24)
- Residential Survey - Epworth-Gilbert-Addoms, 1971-1973 (Box 24)
- Residential Survey - Fraternities, 1971-1973 (Box 24)
- Residential Survey - Giles-House H, 1971-1973 (Box 25)
- Residential Survey - Hanes House, 1971-1973 (Box 25)
- Residential Survey - House P-Stonehenge, 1971-1973 (Box 25)
- Residential Staff - Self-Evaluations, 1975 (Box 25)
- Residential Survey - I - Mirecourt, 1971-1973 (Box 25)
- Residential Survey - Off Campus, 1971-1973 (Box 25)
- Residential Survey - Tabard-Wilson, 1971-1973 (Box 25)
- Residential Survey - Unidentified, 1971-1973 (Box 26)
- Residential Survey - Windsor-York 1971-1973 (Box 26)
- Retreat - Spruce Pines Lodge Map, Undated (Box 26)
- Room Rental Rates, 1968-1971 (Box 26)
- Rush Information, 1968-1973 (Box 26)
- Sensitivity Training, 1969 (Box 26)
- Service Project Ideas (Living/Learning), 1982-1984 and undated (Box 26)
- SHARE (Experimental College Project), 1969-1972 (Box 26)
- SHARE (Financial), 1973-1975 (Box 26)
- Social Regulations, 1966-1969 (Box 26)
- Social Regulations & Information, 1968-1972 (Box 26)
- Speeches - Richard L. Cox, 1970-1971 and undated (Box 26)
- Spring Break, 1972-1973 (Box 26)
- Spring Break Survey (RE: Locking of Dormitories), 1973 (Box 26)
- Southgate Hall (Budget), 1964-1972 (Box 26)
- Staff Lists, 1969-1970 (Box 26)
- Staff Materials, 1968 (Box 26)
- Staff Materials Passed Out to Fraternities, 1968 (Box 26)
- Statistics (Overcrowding in Dormitories), 1959-1970 (Box 27)
- Storage of Personal Items During Breaks/Holidays, 1968-1972 (Box 27)
- Student Emergency Relief Fund, 1954-1961 (Box 27)
- Student - Faculty Administration Council, 1968-1969 (Box 27)
- Student Health Program, 1973-1973 (Box 27)
- Student Mental Health Service, 1972-1973 (Box 27)
- Student Organizations - Blue Jeans (Budget), 1969-1972 (Box 27)
- Student Overcrowding - Durham Hotel, 1977 (Box 27)
- Student Personnel Reports - Forms, 1973 (Box 27)
- Student Records - Policies, 1967-1968 (Box 27)
- Student Refunds & Tuition/Fee Credits, 1969 (Box 27)
- Student-Teacher Problem, 1969 (Box 27)
- Summer Session, 1974-1974 (Box 27)
- Summer Session Correspondence, 1964-1969 (Box 27)
- Summer Session Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 27)
- Summer Session - Reports of Residence Directors & House Counselors, 1959, 1963-1964 (Box 27)
- Summer Session - Reports of Residence Directors & House Counselors, 1967-1969 (Box 27)
- Summer Session - Reports of Residence Directors & House Counselors, 1970-1971 (Box 28)
- Summer Transitional Program, 1973 (Box 28)